sitebuilderreport.com 2019-02-06

# Privacy Policy - Site Builder Report

**Effective July 17, 2017**

**Overview**

This policy sets out how Site Builder Report (“ **we** ” or “ **us** ” or “ **Site Builder Report** ”) uses, protects, and preserves information submitted by users (“ **Users** ” or “ **you** ”) through the SiteBuilderReport.com website (“ **Website** ”). By using Site Builder Report and by submitting information through the Website, you are agreeing to the terms of this policy (“ **Policy** ”). If you have any questions about the Policy, please contact Site Builder Report directly before entering any information by using the [**Contact Form**](https://www.sitebuilderreport.com/contact) provided.

**Definitions**

" **Service** " means all of the services provided by Site Builder Report, including but not limited to all Content, services, and products available through the Website. Site Builder Report is not a financial advisor, and all forms of financial advice or financial services are explicitly excluded from the Service.

" **User** ," “ **you** ” and “ **your** ” refer to the person, company, or organization that has visited or is using our Website and/or our Service.

**Information We Collect and Store**

Site Builder Report will not use any information to contact you for any reason unrelated to your use of the Website. We will not provide this contact information to any third party. We will not use your confidential information for any commercial reason unrelated to the Website. Site Builder Report only collects information that you choose to provide voluntarily, by using the Website.

To learn about your user experience and to make periodic improvements to the Website, we also collect the information regularly collected by web browsers. We will automatically record information and your activity. This may include your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, country, city, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps, system configuration information, metadata concerning your files, and other interactions with the Service.

We also use “cookies” to collect information and improve our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your device. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service.  However, none of this is associated with you as an individual. It is measured only in aggregate. Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of our website.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your information only for purposes of facilitating your use of our webpage and to assist us in improving our service. We do not use your information for any additional or unrelated commercial purposes.

**Surveys**

From time to time, Site Builder Report may conduct surveys via the Website. If you choose to participate, we use your response to come up with the survey results and, sometimes, to publish those results in aggregate on the site. We will never permanently record or report any response you give on its own or connect it to your name or address. We will hold these responses only as anonymous statistics. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.

**Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services**

When you send us an email through the [**Contact Form**](https://www.sitebuilderreport.com/contact) or the [**Issues or Concerns Form**](https://www.sitebuilderreport.com/concerns) provided, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use.

When you request information or other services, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services you requested until you ask us to stop (using the “unsubscribe” instructions provided with each email and/or on the site where you signed up and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. We will not use your address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited message or information (unless that is part of the service you are requesting), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party for such use.

**Linking To Other Sites**

Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Website to another website, the Website Terms of Use and this Policy are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including any site that has a link on the Website, is subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of that site. We encourage you to read the terms of use and privacy policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**How You Can Decide What Communication You’ll Receive From Us**

If you choose to receive them, the Website may periodically send you email messages describing updates, new features, or promotional offers related to the Website. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time. Simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request.

If you do not explicitly choose to receive informational emails, the only email messages you will receive from the Website will be to respond to email inquiries that you send us.

**How to Access, Update or Correct Your Personal Information**

To request access to your personal information stored on the Website, or to modify or delete your personal information, simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request, and we will fulfil your request.

You may also send an email through the [**Contact Form**](https://www.sitebuilderreport.com/contact) provided for us to delete your personal information in a reasonable time after receiving the request.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. The Website uses firewalls and has security measures in place at its physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Website.

**Changes to the Policy**

This Policy was posted on **July 17, 2017**. Site Builder Report reserves the right to change, modify, or amend this Policy at any time. Please also read over the Website [**Terms of Use**](https://www.sitebuilderreport.com/terms-of-use). Site Builder Report takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. Site Builder Report will occasionally update this Policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review Policy updates.

**Contact Us**

Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any Services, you consent to Site Builder Report’s processing of this information as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating.

We encourage you to send inquiries on the Policy and the steps we take to keep your information secure. Please send us an email through the [**Contact Form**](https://www.sitebuilderreport.com/contact) provided.
